<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fragments</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="fc_barcelona">FC Barcelona</string>
    <string name="manchester_city">Manchester City</string>
    <string name="real_madrid">Real Madrid</string>
    <string name="bayern_munich">Bayern Munich</string>


    <string name="barcelona_descr">Futbol Club Barcelona (Catalan pronunciation: [fubˈbɔɫ ˈkɫub bərsəˈɫonə] (About this sound listen)),
        commonly known as Barcelona and familiarly as Barça,[note 1] is a professional football club based in Barcelona, Catalonia, Spain.
        Founded in 1899 by a group of Swiss, English and Catalan footballers led by Joan Gamper, the club has become a symbol of Catalan culture
        and Catalanism, hence the motto "Més que un club" ("More than a club"). Unlike many other football clubs, the supporters own and operate
        Barcelona. It is the second most valuable sports team in the world, worth $3.56 billion, and the world's third richest football club in
        terms of revenue, with an annual turnover of €648.3 million.[2][3] The official Barcelona anthem is the "Cant del Barça", written by Jaume
        Picas and Josep Maria Espinàs.[4]</string>

    <string name="man_city_descr">Manchester City Football Club are a football club in Manchester, England. Founded in 1880 as St. Marks (West Gorton),
    they became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894. The club are based at the Etihad Campus in East Manchester,
    encompassing their 80-acre training facility, Academy Stadium and their home ground, the City of Manchester Stadium which the club moved to in
    2003 having played at Maine Road since 1923.Manchester City first played in the top-tier of the Football League in 1899 and won their first major
    honour with the FA Cup in 1904. The club\'s most successful period was from 1968 to 1970, when they won the League Championship, FA Cup, League Cup
    and European Cup Winners' Cup, under the management team of Joe Mercer and Malcolm Allison. After losing the 1981 FA Cup Final, the club went
    through a period of decline, culminating in relegation to the third tier of English football for the only time in their history in 1998. Having
    regained their Premier League status in the early 2000s, the club were purchased in 2008 by Abu Dhabi United Group for £210 million. Since 2011
    , the club have won seven official honours, including the Premier League in 2012 and 2014.</string>

    <string name="madrid_descr">Real Madrid Club de Fútbol (Spanish pronunciation: [reˈal maˈðɾið ˈkluβ ðe ˈfuðβol]; Royal Madrid Football Club), commonly
    known as Real Madrid, or simply as Real, is a professional football club based in Madrid, Spain.Founded on 6 March 1902 as Madrid Football Club,
    the club has traditionally worn a white home kit since inception. The word Real is Spanish for Royal and was bestowed to the club by King Alfonso
    XIII in 1920 together with the royal crown in the emblem. The team has played its home matches in the 81,044-capacity Santiago Bernabéu Stadium
    in downtown Madrid since 1947. Unlike most European sporting entities, Real Madrid's members (socios) have owned and operated the club throughout
    its history.</string>
    <string name="bayern_descr">Fußball-Club Bayern München e.V., commonly known as FC Bayern München (German pronunciation: [ʔɛf tseː ˈbaɪɐn ˈmʏnçn̩]), FCB,
    Bayern Munich, or FC Bayern, is a German sports club based in Munich, Bavaria (Bayern). It is best known for its professional football team, which
    plays in the Bundesliga, the top tier of the German football league system, and is the most successful club in German football history, having won
    a record 27 national titles and 18 national cups.[4]FC Bayern was founded in 1900 by 11 football players, led by Franz John.[5] Although Bayern won
    its first national championship in 1932,[6] the club was not selected for the Bundesliga at its inception in 1963.[7] The club had its period of
    greatest success in the middle of the 1970s when, under the captaincy of Franz Beckenbauer, it won the European Cup three times in a row (1974–1976)
    . </string>

    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="dialog_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_no">No</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">My Dialog Fragment</string>
    <string name="dialog_text_view">Confirm ?</string>

</resources>
